ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 563-Shoe: Mission: Empleo, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Copies of Stationary, 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Copies of Coffee, 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Coffee Requests (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Job Match: Address Details, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Seminarios, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Copies Extra (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Preparation Seminar (Box 76, Folder 12)
  English and Spanish, No Date
- Copies of Visits Wed/Wed, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Joint Council #13 Shoe Division, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Standard Industrial, Classification, SIC Code (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Close Files, Return Letters, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Job Services/Referrals, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Referrals, 1986-1989 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Retiree Charters, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Retirees and College (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Retiree Conference, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  November 28-29, 1977
- Retiree Conference, 1974-1977 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Retiree Meeting, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Retiree Directors Meeting New York, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  February 23, 1976
- Retiree Discounts, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Retiree Program Directors' Meeting, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Retiree Meeting, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Retired Pension Letters Members, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Retiree Education, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Retiree Center Directors Master List, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Retiree Directors Mailings to, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Retirees Arizona, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Retirees Taxes, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Retired Persons - Mental Health, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Retiree Activities, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Retirees Alabama, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- National Retiree Center Programs, 1973-198- (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Retirees Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Retiree Letters, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Retiree Programs ACWA, 1973-1977 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- Retiree Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Retiree Political Activities, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Retirees Projects, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Retirees Research, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Retirement Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Retirees Rent, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Retired Members United States Congress, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Retiree Information New York, 1973-1976 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Retiree Newsletter, 1973-1977 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Retiree Newsletter Material, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Retiree Nutrition, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Retirees Education, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Retiree Follow Up, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Retirees' Housing, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Retirees Legal Services, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Retiree Legislation, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Retired Members: Letters to, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Lists of Retiree Letters, 1974-1975 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Retiree Directors' Meeting, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  August 17, 1973
- Retiree Program Directors' Meeting, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  May 21-22, 1975
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Committee on Unemployed Members, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Retirees Council, 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- ADOLFO, 1985-1987 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- African-American Labor Center, 1986-1988 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Building and Construction Trades Department, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Committee on Older and Retired Union Members, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Convention, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  October 1987
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Executive Council Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Merger Committee Murray H. Finley, Chairman, 1979-1989 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Miscellaneous State Correspondences, 1986-1989 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: National Industrial Policy Regional Conferences, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: (Regional Conferences), 1988 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union YES, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Bank - Board of Directors and Meetings, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Bank Subscription Agreement, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund - Executive Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund - Investment Committee, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund - Retirement Fund, 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees Insurance Fund, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Clofund), 1987 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- Articles, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Articles, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- American Jewish Congress, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- American Jewish World Service, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- American Jewish World Service Luncheon, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  October 15, 1986
- American Labor Museum, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- American ORT Federation, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company: Investment Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1980-1986 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company: Sigelbaum Correspondence, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- American Apparel Manufacturing Association, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- American Arbitration Association, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- American Greeting Card Company, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- American Income Life Insurance Committee, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Insurance (Clofund): Retirement Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company (Chicago), 1987 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Insurance CLOFUND: Executive Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Insurance: Health Care Cost Containment, 1985-1986 (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Health Care Cost (Clofund) Containment, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Insurance: Investment Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- British North American Committee, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Judge Leon Becker, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Boycott of Conscience, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Briar Neckwear, 1986-1987 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Brookfield, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Canada, 1986-1988 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- British North American Committee: Living and Working Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Canadian American Committee, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs, 1987-1989 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Central America Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Central America, El Salvador, Dave Dyson Material, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Central America - El Salvador, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Central Labor Council, 1985-1987 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Citizen-Labor Energy Coalition, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Coalition of Union Labor Women, 1983-1987 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Columbia University, 1987-1989 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Committee on Political Education (COPE) American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1983-1987 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Priority Contributions, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Special Priority Contributions, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Cornell University, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Priority Contributions, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- General Office Contributions, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Political Contributions, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Community Council of Greater New York: Board of Directors Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- General Office Contributions, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Political Contributions, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Priority Contributions, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Deansgate, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- The Defense Monitor, 1985-1987 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Democratic Convention, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Democratic National Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1985-1988 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Department of State, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Dukakis Campaign, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Dunlop Clothing, Footwear and Textiles, 1986-1987 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Economic Consulting Services Incorporated Stanley Nehmer, 1984-1988 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Economic Policy Council: General Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Economic Policy Council: Debt Issue and Education Panel, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Economic Policy Council: Plenary Agendas, 1986-1988 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Economic Policy Institute, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Elder, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Elder, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Excello, 1986-1987 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Export PAC Bipartisan Coalition for American Exports, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Finley Roast Murray H. Finley, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Material from June 6th Meeting, 1984-1987 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center, 1983-1987 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Histadrut General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Histadrut General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Histadrut General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Histadrut Dinner, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  May 2, 1987
- Histadrut Dinner, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  December 1985
- Houston International University, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board [1 of 4], 1987 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  May 1987
- General Executive Board [2 of 4], 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  March 1987
- General Executive Board [3 of 4], 1987 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  February 1987
- General Executive Board [4 of 4], 1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  January 1987
- Gary Hart, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1983-1987 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board - Committees - Organizing, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board - Committees, Political Action Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board - Committee on Potentially Revised Contracts, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board - Technology Committee, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board - Unemployment Aid Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board - General Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  July 1987
- General Executive Board, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  June 1987
- Gallup Study (Labor Movement), 1988 (Box 84, Folder 24)
- The Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board - Future of the Union Committee, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 26)
- International Rescue Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- IUD - Financial Statements, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- IUD Legislative Conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- IUD- LICIT Principals Meeting, 1981-1987 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Industrial Union Department (IUD) Organizing, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Institute for International Economics, 1986-1987 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- International Association of Clothing Designers, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- International Labor Rights Education Research Fund, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- International Productivity Symposium (Institute of Industrial Engineers), 1987-1988 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- IUD Coordinated Campaign, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- IUD - International Trade Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- IUD Media Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- IUD - Occupational Safety and Health Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- IUD - Olin Committee, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- IUD - Reindustrialization, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- IUD Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- IUD Executive Council Meetings, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Productivity, Target, and Competition Project, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Sub-Committee Meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Industrial Relations Research Association, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- IUD Coordinated Bargaining, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- Local 340, 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Local 340A, 1981-1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Local 365, 1896-1987 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Local 379, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Local 459, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Local 615, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Local 630, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Local 642, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Local 653, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Local 710-T, 1983-1987 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Local 783, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Local 809, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Local 887, 1983-1987 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Local 1418, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Local 1712, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Local 1811, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Local 1855-A, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Made in United States of America, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Dick Morris Consultants, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Local 169, 1977-1987 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Local 178, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 22)
- Local 181, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Local 210, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 24)
- Local 218 Abercrombie, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 25)
- Local 226, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 26)
- Local 237, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 27)
- Local 248 A - C, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 28)
- Local 281, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 29)
- Local 288, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 30)
- Local 324, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 31)
- Jewish Labor Committee - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 32)
- Joint Job Training and Research (JTR), 1985 (Box 86, Folder 33)
- Juvenile Shoe Corporation, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 34)
- The JM Kaplan Fund, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 86, Folder 35)
- Mayor Edward I. Koch, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 36)
- Labor and Employment Law Newsletter, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 37)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1977-1987 (Box 86, Folder 38)
- Locals: General Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 86, Folder 39)
- Local 4, 1982-1985 (Box 86, Folder 40)
- Local 122, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 42)
- Local 143, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 43)
- Local 165, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 44)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: Executive Committee in Antalya, Turkey, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 45)
  October 26-27, 1987
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: ILO Third Tripartite Technical Meeting Geneva, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 46)
  September 2-10, 1987
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: Presidium in New York, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 47)
  August 30-31, 1987
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: Presidium in Brussels, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 48)
  February 26-27, 1987
- Israel, 1984-1987 (Box 86, Folder 49)
- Jewish Forward, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 50)
- Solomon and Rosenbaum (Bernard Ferster), 1983-1987 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- JP Stevens, 1980-1988 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Szold and Brandwen, 1979-1987 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Tahari, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation: Patent Sub-Committee Tailored Clothing Technology, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Telluride Association, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Textile Division Correspondence, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Textile Division Pension Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Philrecorps, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Pioneer Parachute, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Political Action Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Political Letters, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Queens College, 1986-1989 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Asa Philip Randolph Institute, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Reeves Brothers, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Sharing International, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Shearson American Express, 1984-1989 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- New York City and State Managers, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- New York State American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- New York State American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Executive Council Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- New York State American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union Label and Service Trade Department, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Organizing: Meetings, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  February 25, 1985
- Walter A. Peek, 1985-1988 (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Phelps Stokes Fund, 1986-1989 (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Philadelphia Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 26)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 27)
- National Association of Men's Sportswear Buyers Incorporated, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 28)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 29)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multiemployer Plans, 1984-1986 (Box 87, Folder 30)
- National Planning Association: Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 31)
- National Planning Association: Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 32)
- National Planning Association Membership List, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 33)
- National UN Day, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 34)
- Navaco Industries Incorporated, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 35)
- NEB Development Corporation, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 36)
- Workers' Defense League, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Work in America Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Work in America Institute Japan Trip, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  April 1985
- Workmen's Circle Home, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Workplace Health Fund, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Zensen Domei: Japan Federation of Textile Workers Union, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- The Trade Adjustment Assistance Program Extension, 1985-1986 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Treasury Department, 1979-1983 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Trilateral Commission, 1985-1989 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union: Unemployment Aid Fund/Job Match, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Union Label (Dave Dyson), 1987 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- United Hebrew Trades, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- United Housing Foundation, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- US Trade Defense Coalition, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Universalist Church, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- University of Massachusetts, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- University of Rochester, 1986-1987 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Vice Presidents and Managers (Letters to), 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- Washington University, 1986-1988 (Box 88, Folder 19)
- Wingspread Corporation, 1985-1987 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- Wonderknit, 1987-1988 (Box 88, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [1 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [2 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [3 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [4 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [5 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Forms [1 of 6], 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Screening Cards, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Hypertension Screening Cards, 1981-1984 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  Groups of cards are bundled, English and Spanish
- A Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Organization of Retirees, 1987-1988 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Credit Card, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Merger, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union: Retired Vice Presidents, 1985-1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union Retirees (Plaques) (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Administratorship, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Advisory Committee on Trade Negotiations (ACTN), 1989 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Civil Rights Department, 1985-1988 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Advisory Committee on Trade Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Committee on the Evolution of Work: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1985-1989 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Pension Funds, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Constitution, 1981-1987 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Convention, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: General Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Correspondence [1 of 3], 1989 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Correspondence [2 of 3], 1988 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Correspondence [3 of 3], 1987 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Minutes of Meetings Executive Council American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Volume 35, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  Large black binder
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Executive Council Meetings, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Executive Council Meetings, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Executive Council Meeting, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  August 17-19, 1987
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union Label and Service Trades, 1979-1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union Membership, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Union Privilege: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1986-1988 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1983-1989 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Labor/Management Committee, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Maritime Trades Department, 1987-1989 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Pension Investment Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Political Work Committee, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Standing Committees and Executive Council Ad Hoc Committees, 1981-1987 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (CLOfund), 1989 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 2)